Finding Aid for Program in Comparative Study of Social Transformations (University of Michigan) records, 1987-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Working Papers 1987-1997
  - 121. Nicholas B. Dirks, "In Near Ruins: Cultural Theory at the End of the Century," October 1996 (CRSO #548) (Box 2)
  - 122. Agnes Heller, "Critical Theory in a World of Uncertainties," October 1996 (CRSO #549) (Box 2)
  - 123. John Bornemen, "The Production of Minorities and the Rule of Law in Germany and Central European Politics," October 1996 (CRSO #550) (Box 2)
  - 124. Wolfgang Emmerich, "Intellect and Power: Conceptions and Self-Images of the Literary Intelligentsia in Germany Since 1945 and the Influence of Critical Theory," October 1996 (CRSO #551) (Box 2)
  - 125. Konrad H. Jarausch, Hinrich C. Seeba, and David P. Conradt, "The Presence of the Past: Culture, Opinion and Identity in Germany," October 1996 (CRSO #552) (Box 2)
  - 126. Prasenjit Duara, "Of Authenticity and Woman: Personal Narratives of Middle-Class Women in Modern China," November 1996 (CRSO #553) (Box 2)
  - 127. Margaret R. Somers, "Fear and Loathing of the Public Sphere and the Privatization of Citizenship: How to Deconstruct a knowledge Construct," Match 1997 (CRSO #555) (Box 2)
  - 128. Margaret R. Somers, "We're No Angels: Realism, Rational Choice, and Relationality in Social Science," Match 1997 (CRSO #556) (Box 2)
- AV Materials 1990-2001
  AV Materials, 1990-2001 (0.25 linear feet), include two video cassettes featuring speakers Hazel Carby, and Vijay Prashad from the Dean's Lecture Series.
  - Hazel Carby, Dean's Lecture Series October 18, 2000 VHS Videocassette (Box 2)
  - Vijay Prashad, "The Problem of the Twenty-First Century is the Problem of the Colorblind," Dean's Lecture Series March 22, 2001 VHS Videocassette (Box 2)